metalol.net 2019-07-03

# Privacy Policy | MetaLoL

#### Types of Information

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter certain personal information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously, but certain aspects/features may be disabled.

**How We Use Your Personal Information**

The personal information you provide to us will allow us to: contact you if necessary, notify you of site events; promotions; etc., provide our services, and assure site quality persists.

**  How We Protect Your Information**

We employ a variety of security measures through our site host.

**Cookies**

We make use of "cookies," small pieces of data stored on your computer, to maintain a "logged in" status and remember settings you have set up for our site after leaving it. Additionally, advertisements that are managed by third parties which may appear on the Site(s) use cookies. Advertisers use cookies to collect non-personal information when you click on or move your cursor over one of their banner advertisements. You may not realize this information is being collected. Advertisers use this information to monitor the performance of their advertisements. In some cases, we may have access to information from cookies used by these advertisers on the Site(s) and this information may permit us to identify other sites that you have visited that are also associated such advertisers.

Third parties may be placing and reading cookies on your browsers, or using web beacons to collect information as a result of ad serving MetaLoL.  

Google uses the DoubleClick DART cookie on our displaying AdSense for content ads. We, and google, may use this info collected to improve the overall quality of the site and make analysis conclusions.

#### Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not knowingly collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. 

#### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

#### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on January 15th, 2015.

Images and graphics are property of their respective owners. MetaLoL © 2013-2019. All rights reserved. League of Legends and Riot Games Inc. are registered trademarks of Riot Games, Inc.
